50 years have passed.
But I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
Yet the suffering continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Got to get back --
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
They're coming!
Huh?
Aah!!
Look at you.
You've survived worse.
This isn't about
your pathetic little cut.
It's about
that girl you killed.
We've never killed a human
before, have we?
Sure, mountains
of robot corpses.
But this?
This was
the first human being.
Real flesh and blood.
What happens
when the others find you?
You'll have to kill them, too.
Can you?
Will you be able to
when the time comes?
Maybe they will kill you.
Or is that what you want?
No.
Emperor!
Your guards are dead,
and you are next!
Your choices have
clearly led you here,
as have mine.
I will give you
a new choice.
Leave now and live
or stay
and face your destiny.
Ha!
Your Bushido nonsense
means nothing to us.
Your destiny is death!
Huh?
The decisions you make
and the actions that follow
are a reflection
of who you are.
You cannot hide
from yourself.
Death is failure.
Follow the river.
I'll take watch.
Samurai blood.
The river guides
our way.
What...is that?
Quiet!
Mother told us
there would be other creatures.
Wait.
Something else approaches.
Is it with the Samurai?
Should we kill it?
Aku.
It is surely
one of his minions.
It will devour
the weaker one.
What madness is this?
What are they doing?
I...don't know.
Well, I don't like it.
Look.
You have chosen this path.
Life works
in strange ways.
Your choices have clearly
led you here, as have mine.
I will give you
a new choice.
Leave here now and live
or stay
and face your destiny.
Our destiny
is your death!
So...
I guess you're staying.
Perhaps I was unclear.
Enough words!
Show yourself, Samurai,
so you can die!
Very well.
The decisions you make
and the actions that follow
are a reflection of --
Shut up!
...of who you really are.
Aaaaaah!
You worthless scum!
I will kill you!
You can never escape
from Aku!
You will die!
You will die
a horrible death,
and then Aku will sing,
for he is free
from the parasite that you are!
Die, Samurai!
Die, die, you scum!
Die! Die!
Die, Samurai!
You will...diiiiiie!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Back to the past,
Samurai Jack *
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Got to get back,
back to the past *
* Samurai Jack
* Watch out
* Jack, Jack,
Jack, Jack, Jack *
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Samurai Jack
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack